Guide to the Archives of Irish America Vertical Files AIA.013
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- J
  - Jewish Monthly, 2001 (Box 13)
  - John Gabriel Borkman, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - The John McCormack Society of America, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Jones, Mary Harris, 2001 (Box 13)
  - Journal of Prisoners on Prisons, 1996-1997 (Box 13)
  - A Jubilee Celebration Honoring Rev. Leo Clifford, OFM - 50 Years of Ordination, undated (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Judge, Fr. Mychal F., 2001 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Justice for Christy McGrath, circa 2021 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- K
  - Katie Roche (Teresa Deevy), undated (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Kells Publishing Company, circa 1994 (Box 13)
  - Kennedy Child Study Center 17th Annual Spring Benefit, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1963, 1979, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P., II, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Keough-Naughton Institute for Irish Studies, 2003-2008 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Kerryman's Patriotic and Benevolent Association, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - The Keshcarrigan Bookshop, circa 1980-1987 (Box 13)
  - Kilmainham, undated (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - King, Peter, Representative, Long Island, 2010 (Box 13)
  - Knights of Columbus, 1982 (Box 13, Box 4)
  - Knights of the Red Branch, 1922 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Knights of St. Patrick 25th Anniversary, 2013 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - K.R.B. Hall Association, 1909 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - K.R.B. Hall Association Poster, 1920 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 31)
- L
  - Labor Unions: Ireland and New York City, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Ladies of Charity, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Larkin, Jim, 1915 (Box 21)
  - The Lavender and Green Alliance, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Lawe, John E., 1989 (Box 13)
  - "Leaving Ireland" by Francis J. Gallagher, 1995-1996 (Box 13)
  - Lecture Series, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Lectures on Ireland Rebellions (1798, 1848), 1998 (Box 13)
  - Libraries and Archives, circa 2007-2008 (Box 13)
  - Lincoln Center - A Midsummer Night Swing, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Limerickmen's Ledger, circa 1940s to 1960s (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Linen Hall Library, Belfast, undated (Box 13)
  - Lombard, Rosemary, 1998-2017 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Longford Ladies Auxiliary Checks, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Loyal League of the Yiddish Sons of Erin, 1966-1967, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Lynch Dance Tour of Ireland, 1994-1995 (Box 13)
- M
  - MacDonagh, Thomas, undated (Box 21)
  - Mac Stiofain, Sean, 2001 (Box 13)
  - Magazine articles - various topics [2 folders], circa 1971 (Box 21)
  - Make Sectarianism History - International Observers' Report, Northern Ireland, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Makem, Tommy, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Malachy McCourt for Governor, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Manhattan Irish-American Society, 1959-1960 (Box 13)
  - Manning, John B., undated (Box 13)
  - Mario Cuomo and Emerald Society, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Martin Driscoll Irish Art - The Emerald Isle Experience, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Maryland Irish Festival, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Mass of Christian Burial, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Mayo Foundation for the Handicapped, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Mayo Gaelic Football Club of Greater New York Annual Dinner Dance, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - McAliskey, Bernadette Devlin, 1971-1972, 1998 (Box 21, Box 39, Folder 7)
  - McAliskey, Roisin, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
  - The McCabe Fellowship Program, 2010 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - McCain Kennedy Irish Lobby for Immigration Reform Pin, 2017 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - McCarthy, Joe, 2000 (Box 14)
  - McClean Avenue St. Patrick's Day Parade, 2013 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - McCormack, John, 1865, 1928, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Box 44, Folder 6)
  - McCourt, Frank, 1997 (Box 14)
  - McGeough, Gerry, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - McGoldrick's Thread, undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - McGuinness, Martin, 2017 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - McKenna, Siobhan, 1987 (Box 14, Box 39, Folder 13)
  - McKiernan, Eoin, Dr., 1917-2004 (Box 14)
  - McSorley's 150 Year Anniversary Calendar, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Meagher, Thomas Francis, 2010 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Meany, George, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Melbourne and the Irish Famine, 1998 (Box 14)
  - Memorials for the Deceased, 198 (Box 14)
  - Michael Collins [film], 1990-1996 (Box 14)
  - The Michigan Hibernian, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Mick Moloney's Irish Folklore Tours, 1993, 2001-2003 (Box 14, Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Mid-Atlantic Irish (Celtic) Directory, 1998-1999 (Box 14)
  - Mid-Atlantic Irish Organizations, undated (Box 14)
  - Míle Fáilte Radio Program, circa 1991 (Box 14)
  - Mill Hill Fathers [2 folders], 1984-1988 (Box 4)
  - Miriam Nyhan PhD - New York Celtic Memorial Society, 2010 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Moakley, Joseph, 2001 (Box 14)
  - Moll (John B. Keane) Play Program, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Molly Sweeney (Brian Friel), undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Moloney, Michael (Mick) [1 legal-size folder, 1 oversize folder], 1988, 2004 (Box 14, Oversize 24)
  - Moloney, Paddy, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Mother Jones: From Ireland, to America, Back to Ireland, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1947, 1988, 2000-2004 (Box 14)
  - Mulvey, Harold M., 2000 (Box 14)
  - Murphy, Judge Francis T., 1962 (Box 14)
  - Murphy, Maureen, 2001 (Box 14)
  - Museum of the City of New York, 1996 (Box 14)
  - Music: Album of Songs by Victor Herbert. M. Witmark and Sons, New York., 1927 (Box 14)
  - Music Clippings, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Music Companies, Producers and Artists, 1992 (Box 14)
  - Music/Dance Events [2 folders], 1975-2003 (Box 14)
  - Music Lyrics, undated (Box 14)
  - Music Lyrics: "More Than 1000 Songs and Dances of the Irish People", 1976 (Box 14)
  - Music Publications, undated (Box 14)
  - Music Study Programs, circa 1995-1997 (Box 14)
  - Music Tours, 1997 (Box 14)
  - Music: Traditional, circa 1992 (Box 14)
- N
  - National Cathedral of Saint Patrick (Dublin), 2000 (Box 14)
  - National Geographic, 1976 (Box 14)
  - National Irish Freedom Committee: 14th Annual Michael Flannery Testomionial Awards Dinner, 2009 (Box 14)
  - National Library of Ireland, 1994-1996 (Box 14)
  - National Museum of Catholic Art and History, 1999 (Box 21)
  - National Union for Social Justice (membership application), 1934 (Box 14)
  - Newspaper Clipping - Irish Independent, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - New Age Music, 1995 (Box 14)
  - New College of California Irish Studies Program, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - New Hibernia Review, 1996-2007 (Box 14, Box 35, Folder 22)
  - New Ireland Forum, 1983 (Box 21, Box 54, Folder 26)
  - New Irish Works, 1994-1995 (Box 14)
  - New York Celtic Colloquium, 1997 (Box 14)
  - New York City District 22: Ethnic Studies Project, 1979 (Box 14)
  - New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade, 2012 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - New York City Transit Police Department Irish Warpipe Band, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - New York Daily News, 1981 (Box 14)
  - New York Film Festival in its Second Year Spotlights Best of Contemporary Irish Cinema with Six New Features, 2012 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - New York GAA & New York Ladies GAA, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - New York GAA Senior Football Championship Final, 2010 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - The New York Genealogical and Biographical Society, 1998 (Box 14)
  - New York H-Block Armagh Committee, 1983-1987 (Box 14)
  - New York Irish Center, 2004-2017 (Box 14, Box 21, Box 35, Folder 23, Box 40, Folder 4)
  - New York Irish History Roundtable, 1989-2005 (Box 14)
  - New York Journal-American Spring Fashion Editor Contest, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - New York Law School Journal of International and Comparative Law, 1990 (Box 14)
  - New York Magazine, 1971, 1976 (Box 21)
  - New York-New Belfast Conference, 2013 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - New York Philo-Celtic Society, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - New York Police Department/Fire Department of New York, 2002-2007 (Box 14)
  - New York Rose of Tralee Pageant, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - New York Times Magazine -- Bono (signed), 2005 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - The New York Trinity Alumni Association, 1997 (Box 14)
  - New York University, 1994-1999 (Box 14)
  - New York World's Fair, 1964 (Box 14)
  - New York's Oblong, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings (General), circa 1970 (Box 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Irish Echo, 1973-2001 (Box 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings about Irish Language, 1993-2001 (Box 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings: New York Post, 1972-2003 (Box 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings: New York Times (2 folders), circa 1972 (Box 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Small and Local Papers, 1963-2002 (Box 21)
  - The Next Wave (Radio), undated (Box 14)
  - 1916 Societies News, 2010 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Noon, Paddy, 1985 (Box 14)
  - North American Association for Celtic Language Teachers, 1994-2000 (Box 14)
  - North American Buyers Association Inc., 1992-1996 (Box 14)
  - North American Celtic Buyers Association, 1999-2001 (Box 14)
  - North American Distribution of Irish and Low Budget European Tours, 1995 (Box 15)
  - Northern Ireland, 1969-1972, 2000 (Box 21)
  - Northern Ireland: A Role for the United States, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Notre Dame Keough Institute of Irish Studies, 2001 (Box 15)
  - Nuacht a hAon, 1995 (Box 15)
  - NY Young Irelands Camogie Club, 2010 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- O
  - Oatlands Celtic Festival, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
  - O'Brien, J. Kenneth, 1996 (Box 15)
  - Observer Magazine, 1988 (Box 15)
  - The O'Casey Theater Company, 1982, 1993 (Box 21)
  - O'Connell, Emmett, 1936 (Box 15)
  - O'Connor, Cardinal John, 2000 (Box 15, Box 40, Folder 10)
  - O'Connor's Fairways Travel, Inc., 1992 (Box 15)
  - O'Driscoll, William, 2016 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - O'Dwyer, Brian and Marianna, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - O'Dwyer, Paul, 1963-1998 (Oversize 24, Box 15, Box 35, Folder 2000, Box 40, Folder 12)
  - O'Dwyer, William, 1948, 1964 (Box 15, Box 40, Folder 13)
  - O'Faolain, Nuala, 2001 (Box 15)
  - Office of the Council President, City of New York, undated (Box 15)
  - O'Hara, Maureen, 1987 (Box 15)
  - O'Malley, Ernie, 1991-1998 (Box 15)
  - One Ireland One Vote - All Ireland Referendum Now!, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - O'Neill, Eugene, 1986 (Box 15)
  - O'Neill, Thomas "Tip", 1986 (Box 15)
  - Orange Marches/Nationalist Resistance, 2004 (Box 15)
  - O'Reilly, Gerald, 1990 (Box 15)
  - Origin Theatre Company, 2000, 2008-2009, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 11, Box 54, Folder 28)
  - O'Sullivan, Maureen, 1989 (Box 15)
  - Out of the Ashes, 1996 (Box Shared Tamiment 088)
  - Outside Mullingar, 2014 (Box 54, Folder 29)
- P
  - Paddy Keehan & John Walsh, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Paddyology, 1992 (Box 15)
  - Pangur's Quest (Glucksman Ireland House), 2013 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Parish of Saint Ann, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Patterson, Frank, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Payne, Donald M., 2010 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - The Pearse Commemoration Committee of New York, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Pelican Publishing Company, 1997-1998 (Box 15)
  - Penguin Putnam Inc., 1994 (Box 15)
  - Petition for American Citizenship, 1820 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group's Annual Traditional Irish Music & Dance Festival, 1993-1999 (Box 15)
  - Philadelphia, Here I Come! (Brian Friel), 1994 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Philadelphia Immigration Resource Center, 2001 (Box 15)
  - Photography Exhibitions, undated, 1999-2000 (Box 15)
  - Pittsburgh Irish Festival, 1996-1998 (Box 15)
  - Plain Truth Ministries, 1982 (Box 21)
  - The Playboy of the Western World (J.M. Synge), 2004 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Pluto Press, 1987 (Box 15)
  - Poblacht Na h:Eireann War News, 1922 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Poetry, 1976, 1996-1998 (Box 15)
  - Political Cartoons, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Political Education Committee, 1995 (Box 15)
  - Political/Radical Publications, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Politics: Irish, undated (Box 15)
  - Politics: Irish American, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Postcard - The Signing of the Proclamation Easter 1916, undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Postcards, 1929, 1996 (Box 15, Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Prayer Card - Diamond Jubilee of Saint Leo's Church, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Price, Marion, 2012 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Project Irish Outreach, 1990 (Box 15)
  - Public Art Tour - Irish Hunger Memorial, undated (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Publishers: Canada, 2004 (Box 15)
  - Publishers: Ireland, 1995-1999 (Box 15)
  - Publishers: United Kingdom, 1992 (Box 15)
  - Publishers: United States (A-H), circa 1975-2001 (Box 15)
  - Publishers: United States (I-Q), 1977-2004 (Box 15)
  - Publishers: United States (R-U), circa 1981-2001 (Box 15)
  - Pubs/Bars and Restaurants, 1980 (Box 15)
- Q
  - Quain, Robert F., undated (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - The Quarterdeck, 2012 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Queensland Irish Association, 1948, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Quinn, Carmel, 1957, 1999 (Box 15)
  - Quinn, Christine C., 2010 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Quinn, D.P., undated (Box 15)
- R
  - Radio Specials of Irish Interest, 1991-1993 (Box 15)
  - Re-Imagining Ireland Advance Program, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Recording Labels, 1963 (Box 15)
  - Regent Graphics, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
  - Rego Irish Records [2 folders], 1980 (Box 15)
  - Reid, Rev. Sean -- "Reflection on Some Sixty Years", undated (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Relatives for Justice (Northern Ireland), 2009 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Remarks of Timothy B. Driscoll, Esq., 2012 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Reports of Northern Ireland Investment, 2010 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Republic of Ireland Defense Fund, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Republican Sinn Fein, 1992 (Box 22)
  - The Rights of Man: The Concert for Joseph Doherty, 1991 (Box Shared Tamiment 084, Audiocassette 013.0001)
  - Riot Photographs, undated (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Rising Labor Commonwealths, 1918 (Box 15)
  - Riverdance, 1996 (Box 15, Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Roberts Rinehart Publishers, 1994-1998, undated (Box 15)
  - Robinson, Mary, 1997 (Box 16)
  - Rockland County AOH 2006 Emerald Ball (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Rocky Mountain Irish Festival, 2015 (Box Shared Tamiment 029, Folder 5)
  - Rogers, James, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Rosalind Walshe Collection, 1999 (Box 16)
  - Rose of Tralee Metropolitan New York Committee, 1977, 1992 (Box 16)
  - Royal Irish Academy, 1997-1999 (Box 16)
- S
  - Saint Brendan's Annual Irish Day Parade and Festival, 1992 (Box 16)
  - Saint Brendan - Voyage, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Saint Brigid's Church, 2006 (Box 16)
  - Saint Jerome's Church, 1943, undated (Box 16)
  - Saint Martin's Press, 1990-2002 (Box 16)
  - Saint Mary's University, 1995-1999 (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick Fathers: Annual Dance, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick Fathers: Annual Dance, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Saint Patrick Society of Brooklyn, 1974-1977 (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick Society of Quad Cities, 1997 (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick Society of Queens, 2002 (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick's Cathedral, 1942 (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick's Day, 1977-2018 (Box 16, Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Cards, undated (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Celebration: Ticonderoga, NY, 1866 (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick's Day: New York City Ball, 1991-1995 (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Brooklyn Irish American Parade Committee, Inc. [6 folders], 1977, 1987-2006 (Box 16, Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade and Celebration Committee [6 folders], 1971-2004 (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade and Celebration Committee Scholarship, 1991 (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade and Celebration Committee Line of March, undated (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade Committee: Arizona, 1995 (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade Committee, West Orange (program), 2010 (Box 21)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Emmetsburg Saint Patrick's Association, 1991 (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Mineola Irish-American Society of Nassau, Suffolk, and Queens, Inc. [3 folders], 1976, 1987-2004 (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Mid-Hudson Saint Patrick's Day Parade, 2000 (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: New York City, 1981-2018 (Box 17, Box 36, Folder 8-9, Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parde -- Filmed by Arthur C. Kenteir, circa 1954-1957; cuid44004 (Box Shared Tamiment 176, 8mm film reel cuid44004)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parades: New York City (program), 2009 (Box 21)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Newark Saint Patrick's Day Parade Committee, Inc., 1994 (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Nutley Irish-American Association, 2004 (Box 18)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Queens County Saint Patrick's Day Parade and Cultural Committee [4 folders], 1995-2005 (Box 18)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Syracuse Saint Patrick's Day Parade Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 18)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Tarrytown and Sleepy Hollow Saint Patrick's Day Parade, 2001 (Box 18)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: WPIX, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Yonkers Saint Patrick's Day Parade Committee [2 folders], 1986 (Box 18)
  - Saint Patrick's Old Cathedral, 1999 (Box 18)
  - Saint Rita's Parish, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Salon Éire 100, 2016 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Sands, Bobby, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Sanger, Margaret Higgins, 1999 (Box 18)
  - Scalamandre, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Scanlon, John, 2001 (Box 18)
  - Schade Academy of Irish Dance, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Scoil Gaeilge Ghearóid Tóibín, 1993-1998 (Box 18)
  - Scoil Gaeilge Mhichil uí Locháín, 1996-1998 (Box 18)
  - Scotch-Irish Society, 2018-2019 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Scottish Lion Import Shop, 1997-2000 (Box 18)
  - Sculptured Lives, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Sean Benson #1, 2005 (Box Shared Tamiment 084, Audiocassette 013.0002)
  - Sean Benson #2, 2005 (Box Shared Tamiment 084, Audiocassette 013.0003)
  - Sean McBride Reception Invitation, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Sean Oglaigh na hEireann, 2014-2015 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - The Searing-Roslyn United Methodist Church, 1996-2001 (Box 18)
  - Sectarianism on Parade, 2005 (Box 18, Box 41, Folder 4)
  - "A Sense of Ireland" (publication), 1980 (Box 21)
  - The Session! - A Conference on Irish & Irish American Music & Entertainment, 2012 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - The Shamrock Ballroom, circa 1950 (Box 18)
  - Shamrock Gift Shop, undated (Box 18)
  - The Shanachie (Connecticut Irish American Historical Society), 1994 (Box 18)
  - Shanachie Records Corporation, 1977-1997 (Box 18)
  - Shanley, Father Timothy J., 1991, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Shannon Duty Free Shopping, 1997 (Box 18)
  - Shannon Gaels Supporters Club Field of Dreams, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Sharkey, John Alfred "Alfie", 2010 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Sheridan, General Philip H., 1985 (Box 18)
  - Shillelagh Sentinel, 2012 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Six Facets of Ireland (New York Public Library), 2010 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Sixty Irish Songs (William Arms Fisher), undated (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Shriver, Maria, 2000 (Box 18)
  - Sinn Fein, 1906, 1981, undated (Box 18)
  - The Sixth Annual International Theatre Festival, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Slieve Bawn Handcraft Co-operative Supporters, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - The Slievenmanset Dancing Club, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Smith, Captain James, 1986 (Box 18)
  - Social Democratic and Labour Party, 2002 (Box 21)
  - Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick, 1924-1940 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
  - The Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick - 57th Annual Luncheon, 2012 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick (Long Island): Annual Luncheon, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick - Baltimore, MD, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick in New York City: Charter, Constitution, By-Laws, etc. [3 folders], 1922 (Box 8)
  - Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick in New York City: Anniversary Dinner Seating lists, 1966-1967, 1974, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick in New York City: Anniversary Dinner Programs (with gaps), 1966-1989 (Box 8)
  - Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick in New York City, 1975-1997 (Box 8)
  - Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick in New York City: Yearbooks, 1995-1996 (Box 8)
  - Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick - Westchester County, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Songs of the Irish Union Soldier, 1861-1865, 1998 (Box 18)
  - The Soldier's Song Waltons' Piano and Musical Instrument Galleries, Dublin, undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Solemn Vespers, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Song Lyrics, undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Special, 1976-2003 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Special events, 1984-2018 (Box 36, Folder 3-5)
  - Spellman, Cardinal Francis, 1956 (Box 18)
  - Spirit of Ireland (Irish Arts Center), 2013 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Sporting Events, 1992-1999 (Box 18)
  - Spudchucker Collective, 1994, undated (Box 18)
  - St. Barnabus Church 100th Anniversary, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - St. Jerome Parish Presents an Irish Celebration, 2012 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - St. Nathy's College Journal, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - St. Pat's for All, 2013 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - St. Patrick's Catholic Mission, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - St. Patrick's Celebration & Dance of the Galway's Men S&B Ass'n Inc., 1978 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - St. Patrick's Committee of Holyoke, Inc., 1995-2000 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade and Celebration Committee, 2014 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade Committee, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade: Baltimore, Maryland, 1995-2009 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade -- Grand Marshall and Aides Reception Program, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade -- Grand Marshall and Aides Reception Program, 2012 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade -- Grand Marshall and Aides Reception Program, 2018 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - St. Patrick's Dinner - Dance, the Galway Men's S&B Ass'n Inc., 1990 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - St. Paul's Chapel, 2016 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - The Stone Street Press, 1994-1995 (Box 18)
  - The Story of Ireland (Dion Boucicault), 1881 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - The Story of Knock (Rev. Fr. James, O.F.M. Cap.), 1950 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Stylus Publishing, 1998-2001 (Box 18)
  - Sullivan, Ed, undated (Box 18)
  - Swinford GAA Club, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Syracuse University Press, circa 1998 (Box 18)
- T
  - Tara Circle, 1992-2000 (Box 18, Box 38)
  - Teilifis na Gaeilge (Network Ireland Television), undated (Box 18)
  - Television: Irish and Irish American Roles, 1998 (Box 18)
  - Television Programs of Irish Interest, 1992-1999 (Box 18)
  - Telling Our Irish Stories, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Telling Our Stories: Oral Histories and Irish America (New York Public Library), 2013 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Tereshchuk, David, 2001 (Box 18)
  - Theater: Broadway Productions: A-C, 1983-1999 (Box 18)
  - Theater: Broadway Productions: D-F, 1982-1999 (Box 18)
  - Theater: Broadway Productions: H-M, 1981-2000 (Box 18)
  - Theater: Broadway Productions: P-S, 1966-2007 (Box 18)
  - Theater: Broadway Productions: T-U, 1995-1999 (Box 18)
  - Theater: Broadway Productions: W, 1988-1999 (Box 18)
  - Theater: Broadway Reviews, 1963 (Box 19)
  - Theater: Off-Broadway Productions: G-M, 1946-1992 (Box 19)
  - Theater: Off-Broadway Productions: O-W, 1946-2004 (Box 19)
  - Theater: Off-Off-Broadway [3 folders], 1988-1998 (Box 19)
  - Theater: Small Productions [1 legal-size folder, 1 oversize folder], 1975 (Box 19)
  - Theatre Omnibus, 1996-; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - Thomas Davis Irish Players, 1982, 1995 (Box 19)
  - Thornton, John J., 1990 (Box 19)
  - 'Though Dead He Yet Speaketh': Abolitionist Memories of Daniel O'Connell in the United States, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Tom Geraghty Association, undated (Box 19)
  - Tommy Makem's Irish Pavillion, 1991-1993 (Box 19)
  - Trade Exhibitions [2 folders], 1992-1998 (Box 19)
  - A Traditional Irish Christmas with the Chieftans (Lincoln Center Program), 1981 (Box 44, Folder 26)